{"test_questions": [[{"question": "What device is similar to an RTD but has a negative temperature coefficient?", "opta": "Strain gauge", "optb": "Thermistor", "optc": "Negative-type RTD", "optd": "Thermocouple", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The resistive change of a strain gauge", "opta": "is based on the weight placed upon it, but can be many thousands of ohms", "optb": "is usually no more than 100", "optc": "is based on the gauge factor, but is typically less than an ohm", "optd": "has a positive temperature coefficient", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The silicon-controlled rectifier can be turned off", "opta": "by a negative gate pulse", "optb": "by forced commutation", "optc": "with the off switch", "optd": "when the breakover voltage is exceeded", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The output voltage of a typical thermocouple is", "opta": "less than 100 mV", "optb": "greater than 1 V", "optc": "Thermocouples vary resistance, not voltage.", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The connections to a thermocouple", "opta": "can produce an unwanted thermocouple effect, which must be compensated for", "optb": "produce an extra desirable thermocouple effect", "optc": "must be protected, since high voltages are present", "optd": "produce an extra desirable thermocouple effect and must be protected, since high voltages are present", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the zero-voltage switch used for?", "opta": "To reduce radiation of high frequencies during turn-on of a high current to a load", "optb": "To control low-voltage circuits", "optc": "To provide power to a circuit when power is lost", "optd": "For extremely low-voltage applications", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Temperature sensing can be achieved by the use of", "opta": "thermocouples", "optb": "RTDs", "optc": "thermistors", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The purpose of compensation for a thermocouple is", "opta": "to decrease temperature sensitivity", "optb": "to increase voltage output", "optc": "to cancel unwanted voltage output of a thermocouple", "optd": "used for high-temperature circuits", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The change in value of an analog signal during the conversion process produces what is called the", "opta": "quantization error", "optb": "resolution error", "optc": "Nyquist error", "optd": "sampling error", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following performance specifications applies to a sample-and-hold circuit?", "opta": "Aperture time", "optb": "Aperture droop", "optc": "Feedback", "optd": "Acquisition jitter", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "RTDs are typically connected with other fixed resistors", "opta": "in a pi configuration", "optb": "in a bridge configuration", "optc": "and variable resistors", "optd": "and capacitors in a filter-type circuit", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Holding current for an SCR is best described as", "opta": "the minimum current required for turn-off", "optb": "the current required before an SCR will turn on", "optc": "the amount of current required to maintain conduction", "optd": "the gate current required to maintain conduction", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the moving part of a linear variable differential transformer?", "opta": "Primary", "optb": "Secondary", "optc": "Diaphragm", "optd": "Core", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}